♪Looking in the mirror,
my temples have turned white♪
♪Taking off the hairpins and makeup,
shedding the disguise♪
♪A cold face♪
♪With two lines of tears♪
♪If an actor could gain pity♪
♪The audience offers sincere words♪
♪Perhaps the story could be changed♪
♪The storyteller says♪
♪This mortal world is full of turmoil♪
♪Within sight but beyond reach♪
♪Yet I still don't want to give up♪
♪Don't let the memory be hollowed out♪
♪Don't make me ridiculous♪
♪Some vows turn into smoke
and fade away♪
♪Even the leaves know when autumn comes,
but you don't even know me♪
♪Imprisoned in plight,
yet still full of passion♪
♪I mock this absurd and entangled love♪
♪How can I bear to let go♪
=Whispers of Southern Song=
=Episode 16=
(Ghost)
Governor,
our people have sent words.
Jiang Chun'er replaced Song Mianxiang,
President Jiang's real killer,
and is being held in prison.
Xu You'an is unaware of that now.
Heaven is helping us!
Just go
and make sure Jiang Chun'er dies
on the execution ground tomorrow.
Yes.
(My Jiang family has wronged you all.)
(So let me die in your stead.)
(Once Death claims this debt of sin,)
(I hope you can forgive my family.)
Song Mianxiang.
Execute her!
Kill her!
(Her Death is Fengcheng's Peace)
Adjutant Sun, what's going on?
Didn't we already
reveal the truth to the public?
Why do they
still hate Song Mianxiang so much?
They only saw the knife she raised,
but didn't see that beneath her knife
were blood-soaked monsters
disguised as men.
Because the clamor of the opera
had dressed them up as respectable folk.
Execute her!
Kill her!
Miss Jiang?
Chun'er?
Stop!
Dr. Song!
Are you alright?
I lay out the indictment with my life
and write their sins in blood,
only hoping to bring the truth
of that unjust case
from eight years ago to light.
I killed Jiang Xiaoren.
But his death
is far from enough to repay the debt
of over 60 lives from eight years ago.
So this is the blood indictment
she spoke of?
Those are names of over 60 people.
Oh, my!
That's so pitiful!
I was abducted and taken
to the Jiang family when I was fifteen.
The other abducted girls and I
were just living toys to Jiang Xiaoren
for others' amusement
in exchange for profits.
Jiang Xiaoren committed such evil deeds
only because he had the backing
of Xu Fan and the Xiaosheng Society.
They protected each other,
colluding in villainy.
They feared the truth would be exposed,
so they cruelly killed everyone
and framed Zhao Shengge
as the murderer in the serial killings
eight years ago,
burying both the truth
and the injustice.
Who fired the shot?
What happened?
Dr. Song?
Dr. Song!
I saw it! Someone
from the Xiaosheng Society fired!
Adjutant Sun,
have this place surrounded.
Yes.
Dr. Song.
My name is Yu Xiangling.
I was born into a family of doctors,
not a commodity.
I know.
I'm an innocent person.
Dr. Song!
Fengqiu,
think of your daughter.
She is still so young.
She can't be without her mother.
- Chun'er.
- Fengqiu.
Take this, and leave
with this gentleman.
Mother.
We go together.
Senior, you go first.
Jiang Xiaoren abducted dozens of women,
trading them like commodities.
I must go save them
and take them with me.
Go quickly!
Fengqiu!
Senior,
go quickly.
No,
Fengqiu!
You know too much.
Where do you think you're going?
Fengqiu,
hurry and go!
- Senior!
- Take Chun'er and go!
Go!
Catch her.
Yes!
After them!
Hurry!
This way! Hurry!
Mother, I'm scared.
Don't be scared.
I'm here.
Let's go.
Mother, I'm scared.
Don't be scared. Let's go.
(Account Book)
Come on.
Go inside.
Mother!
Let go of my mother!
Get away!
Don't touch my child!
Let go of my mother!
Get away!
(Woman's Plea at Paramount
Reveals the True Culprit)
President Jiang,
as you instructed,
tomorrow's headline
in the Fengcheng Daily will be this.
President Jiang,
Paramount has been closed down
as you ordered
and will become a modern girls' school.
Let's call it Fengxiang Girls' School.
All girls can study there
to create a different future
for themselves.
President,
all our shops have been ransacked.
And some members have left the society.
The situation is dire.
You let a rabble of fools rattle you?
How dare a bunch of scoundrels
raise their flags here?
Xu You'an,
how dare you trespass
into the Xiaosheng Society!
Trespass?
Governor Mansion rules
the whole Fengcheng.
You greedy, heartless,
women-abducting,
and murderous beasts!
Now that the truth is out,
you're still acting tough?
Nonsense!
This is solid proof of your vile deeds.
Still denying it?
You keep a pack of dogs,
and you dare to strut around here?
A brat born of a dancing girl,
and you really think
you're the Governor?
Say that again!
If you dare to strike,
I'll make all the people of Fengcheng
die with me.
Xu You'an!
If they are not eradicated,
only the commoners will suffer.
For now, it's better not to act rashly.
♪As if it were fate♪
♪Deliberately playing tricks♪
♪We miss each other♪
♪Creating a turbulent drama♪
♪And a bizarre♪
♪Anonymous legend♪
♪The plot twists and turns♪
♪Play out over and over again♪
♪Waiting to be discarded♪
♪And you are like a moth to the flame♪
♪Refuse to submit♪
♪I can't bear to blame you♪
♪There are always too many♪
♪Helpless situations♪
♪Overwhelmed by time♪
♪Even if I have questions♪
♪I harbor desires♪
♪Nowhere to find answers♪
♪People come and go♪
♪I'm still all alone♪
♪Wandering around♪
♪Fortunate to have you with me♪
♪Go through the entanglement♪
♪If longing♪
♪Turns into dust and smoke♪
♪How can I be at ease♪
♪Having walked through prosperous times♪
♪And travelled around the world♪
♪Scars all over me♪
♪If longing never fades♪
♪Burns still hot♪
♪Let it turn into dust and smoke♪
♪After half a lifetime of loneliness♪
♪In the next life♪
♪Entangle with you again♪